https://www.polepositionmarketing.com/privacy/

Privacy
Homepage >
Privacy
This privacy policy covers all Pole Position Marketing web properties. Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to our users’ privacy, we disclose the following information.
What personally identifiable information Pole Position Marketing collects.
What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the Website.
What organization collects the information.
How Pole Position Marketing uses the information.
With whom Pole Position Marketing may share user information.
What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.
What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Pole Position Marketing control.
How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection and Use
Pole Position Marketing is the sole owner of the information collected on our website. Pole Position Marketing collects information at several different points on our Website.
Non-personal clickstream information is collected about all users for the purpose of general tracking of web traffic to our site. Additional personal information is collected through an optional website form when prospective customers request information, download content or subscribe to email marketing. Users have the option to participate in this activity for the purpose of contacting by email or regular mail. A user must provide the clickstream information (internet protocol address, internet service provider, platform type, date/time stamp, operating system), http protocol information (last uri requested and browser type), interaction information (browser interaction such as when the mouse moves over an image), computer information (computer and browser information), state management mechanisms (data allowing a user to be tracked consistently), search terms (search text), user’s name, user’s employer, user’s business contact information, business/organization name and contact information for the business/organization. It is optional for the user to provide User’s Name, User’s Employer, User’s Business Contact Information, Business/Organization Name and Contact Information for the Business/Organization. We encourage users to provide optional information so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site. The reason we use this information is to complete the current transaction, contact by email or regular mail, enhance our site and product offerings and maintain and secure our site. We retain this information for an indeterminate period of time.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user’s hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. You can set your browser to notify you to either accept or deny the cookie according to the following information.
in IE6, see Microsoft’s Internet Explorer Web Privacy page.
in Netscape 6, see Netscape 6 – Safety with More Control.
in Opera 5 or 6, see Opera Preferences: Privacy.
Our website uses cookies to enhance our site.
Profiles
Pole Position Marketing does not use or create users profiles that store information for visitors. Client profiles are created and held in a secure portion of the site.
Communications from the Site
When customers provide us contact information for Website (user participation is voluntary) we use the information to contact the user to deliver sales and product information that will be useful to the them.
Sharing Information
Legal Disclaimer
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our website.
Personally Identifiable Information
Personally identifiable information is not shared with any third parties.
Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)
Aggregate information may be shared with third parties for the sole purpose of marketing by and for Pole Position Marketing’s services. Your information will never be sold.
Data Security
Pole Position Marketing has physical security in our facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information. Our company does not handle sensitive financial or health related information.
Correcting, Updating, Deleting and/or Deactivating Personal Information
If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address) they cannot change information we collect. If a user wishes to correct/update information or no longer desires our service, they can notify us of what they desire by contacting us using any of the information in the Contact section of this policy.
Links and Advertisements
Our website contains links to other sites. We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. We, Pole Position Marketing, are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Website.
Changes to the Privacy Statement
The information you submit to us is controlled by the privacy policy in effect at the time you submit it. If we significantly change our policy, we will post a notice in a conspicuous place on our website notifying visitors of policy changes.
Contact Information
You may contact us if you have questions about our privacy policy.
Resolving Privacy Policy Disputes
If you think we have not followed our privacy policy in some way, it can be resolved by contacting us.
Ask The Pit Crew
Do you have a question you need answered by an expert?
Ask Now
